Guide to the Richard Smalley papers, 1943-2007, bulk 1990-2005 MS 490
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Richard Smalley papers
1943-2007
1990-2005
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Smalley, Richard E., 1943-2005
MS 490
16 Linear Feet
The papers of Nobel Prize winning chemist and physicist Richard E. Smalley are comprised of the lectures, presentations and supporting materials leading to Smalley's discovery of fullerenes, which eventually lead to his Nobel Prize. Included are lectures and presentations, conferences attended, awards received, and articles written. Copies of Dr. Smalley's actual laboratory research notes and materials are included. The papers also include personal memorabilia. Smalley was affiliated with Rice University from 1976 until his death in 2005.
(18 boxes)
Biographical Note
Richard E. Smalley was affiliated with Rice University from 1976 until his death in 2005, serving as the Gene and Norman Hackerman Professor of Chemistry at Rice beginning in 1982 and Professor of Physics at Rice beginning in 1990. A co-founder of the Rice Quantum Institute in 1979, he served as its chairman beginning in 1986, and was the director of the Center for Nanoscale Science and Technology. He was a member of the National Academy of Sciences (elected 1990), the American Academy of Arts and Sciences (elected 1991), and was the recipient of the 1991 Irving Langmuir Prize in chemical physics, the 1992 International Prize for New Materials (shared with R.F. Curl and H.W. Kroto), the 1992 E.O. Lawrence Award of the U.S. Department of Energy, the 1992 Robert A. Welch Award in Chemistry, the 1993 William H. Nichols Medal, and the 1996 Nobel Prize in Chemistry (shared with R.F. Curl and H.W. Kroto).
Smalley pioneered advances in the development of supersonic beam laser spectroscopy, super-cold pulsed beams, and laser-driven sources of free radicals, triplets, and metal and semiconductor cluster beams. He discovered and characterized fullerenes, the third elemental form of carbon after graphite and diamond, for which he was awarded the Nobel Prize.
Born June 6, 1943, in Akron, Ohio, Smalley received his bachelor's degree in chemistry in 1965 from the University of Michigan, and master's and doctorate degrees from Princeton University in 1971 and 1973.
Scope and Contents
The Richard E. Smalley Papers comprise the lectures, presentations and supporting materials leading to Smalley's discovery of fullerenes, which eventually lead to his Nobel Prize. Included are lectures and presentations, conferences attended, awards received, and articles written. Copies of Dr. Smalley's actual laboratory research notes and materials are included. The papers also include personal memorabilia.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586. Box 18 stored onsite in the vault at Woodson Research Center.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research. Series XI, the copies of Dr. Smalley's research notes, are restricted. Permission to view these materials must be obtained from the Rice University Office of the General Counsel.
Acquisition Information
The Richard Smalley Papers were received on Sept. 26, 2000 from Carter Kittrell, Rice Chemistry Department research scientist, after Richard Smalley had placed them in storage. Additional materials were received in 2010 and 2015 from the Richard E. Smalley Institute for Nanoscale Science and Technology.
General
Dr. Smalley's Nobel Prize is not held by the Woodson Research Center. The Nobel Prize was framed and displayed in the Smalley Institute for Nanoscale Science & Technology. The certificate for the prize is in the WRC vault.
Related Materials
Materials related to the Richard Smalley Academic Papers can be found in the Smalley Institute for Nanoscale Science and Technology Records (UA 184, Woodson Research Center, Fondren Library, Rice University).
Index Terms
Subjects
Nobel prizes; Laser spectroscopy; Chemists; Fullerenes; Nanotechnology; Universities and colleges
Document Types
articles; journals (periodicals); lecture notes; letters (correspondence)
- Series I: Lectures, Presentations, and Conferences, 1990-1993; 249640
  Scope and Contents note
  Events attended by Dr. Smalley in the capacity of moderator, panelist or other official.
  - Office of Naval Research, Semiconductor Cluster Surface Chemistry, Jan. 21-23, 1990; 249774 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Society for Mass Spectrometry, Advances Toward a General FT-ICR Approach to Cluster Surface Science, Jan. 28-31, 1990; 249773 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science,: Buckminsterfullerene, Feb. 15-20, 1990; 249772 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Baylor University Chemistry Department, and Other Strange Beasts from the Land of Supersonic Beams, Feb. 23, 1990; 249771 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - University of Houston Physics Department, Nano cluster Surfaces: Chemistry & Physics, March 6, 1990; 249770 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Physical Society, In Search of Special Structures, March 12-16, 1990; 249769 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Department of Energy Sciences' Catalysis and Surface Chemistry Research, March 26-28, 1990; 249768 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Combustion Dynamics Facility Workshop, April 5-7, 1990; 249767 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Chemical Society, Studies of Cluster Surface Chemistry, April 22-27, 1990; 249766 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Soot and Stars, April 24, 1990; 249765 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Army Research Office, Gas Phase Probes of Gallium Arsenide Cluster Chemistry, May 9-11, 1990; 249764 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - University of Minnesota Department of Chemistry,Tinker Toy Surface Science,Past and Future Spectral Probes of Clusters, Soot, and Stars, May 14-18, 1990; 249763 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Atomic, Molecular and Optical Sciences, May 20, 1990; 249762 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - American Society for Mass Spectrometry, FT-ICT and the Future of Cluster Surface Science, June 3-8, 1990; 249761 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - High Temperature Chemistry Gordon Research Conference, Refractory Cluster Beams, July 23-27, 1990; 249760 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - American Chemical Society, Cluster Surface Chemistry via FT-ICR, Aug. 27-29, 1990; 249759 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Frontiers of Materials Sciences, Clusters of Silicon, Germanium and Diamond, Oct. 26, 1990; 249758 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Pacific Northwest Laboratories Workshop, Nov. 19-20, 1990; 249757 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Materials Research Society, Laser Annealing of Semiconductor Clusters: Silicon Nanocrystals, Nov. 26-30, 1990; 249756 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - IBM Almaden Physical Science Colloquium, Surface Chemistry and Physics of Levitated Clusters, Dec. 6, 1990; 249755 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - National Institute of Standards and Technology, Formation and Properties of C 60 and the Fullerenes, Dec. 6-7, 1990; 249754 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - University of California San Diego Chemistry Department, C 60, Chapter 2, Jan. 22, 1991; 249753 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Texas Instruments, Carbon Fullerenes, Jan. 31, 1991; 249752 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Texas A&M Physics Department, C 60, Chapter II, Feb. 27, 1991; 249751 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Naval Research Laboratory, Surface Chemistry of Laser Annealed Clusters, March 13, 1991; 249750 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - American Physical Society, C 60-Chapter 2, March 18-22, 1991; 249749 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Indiana University, C 60: Chapter 2, March 28, 1991; 249748 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Johns Hopkins University, C 60: Chapter Two, March 29, 1991; 249747 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - American Chemical Society, Surface Chemistry of Laser-Annealed Clusters, April 14-19, 1991; 249746 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - NATO Advanced Research Workshop, Surface Chemistry and Photophysics of Levitated Clusters, April 19-26, 1991; 249745 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - National Academy of Sciences, April 28-May 1, 1991; 249744 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Smithsonian Institution, Breakthrough in Chemistry: Buckyballs, May 1, 1991; 249743 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - James Franck Institute (University of Chicago), Buckminsterfullerene: Chapter 2, May 7, 1991; 249742 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Quatum Electronics Laser Science, Image-Charge Bound States of Metal Clusters, May 13-17, 1991; 249741 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Shell Development Co., Buckyballs, May 22, 1991; 249740 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Michigan State University, C 60: Chapter 2, May 31, 1991; 249739 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - GE Corporate Research Division, June 17, 1991; 249738 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - National Research Council Canada, Buckyballs, June 18-20, 1991; 249737 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Dow Chemical Co., Buckyballs, June 21-22, 1991; 249736 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Gordon Research Conference on Metal and Semiconductor Clusters, Aug. 5-9, 1991; 249735 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - American Chemical Society, Aug. 25-30, 1991; 249734 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Rotary Club of River Oaks, Sept. 10, 1991; 249733 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - American Chemical Society, Buckyballs, Sept. 12, 1991; 249732 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Lawrence Berkeley Laboratory, Sept. 13-14, 1991; 249731 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - University of Arizona, Doping the Fullerenes, Sept. 18, 1991; 249730 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Loyola University, Oct. 3, 1991; 249729 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - International Symposium on Physics and Chemistry of Finite Systems, C 60 Today, Oct. 8-12, 1991; 249728 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Electrochemical Society, Doping Bucky, Oct. 13-17, 1991; 249727 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - American Institute of Physics Corporate Associates, Buckyballs, Oct. 22, 1991; 249726 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - University of Houston College of Natural Sciences and Mathematics, Buckyballs, Oct. 26, 1991; 249725 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - UCLA, Beyond Bucky, Oct. 31, 1991; 249724 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Rice University Fund Council, Buckyballs, Nov. 1, 1991; 249723 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Amsterdam Chemistry conference, Reactivity of Metal Clusters, Nov. 13-15, 1991; 249722 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Electrochemical Society, Doping Buckyballs-New Forms of Elemental Carbon, Nov. 21, 1991; 249721 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Materials Research Society, Dec. 3-4, 1991; 249720 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Taipei Taiwan Industrial Technology Research Institute, Jan. 3-9, 1992; 249719 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Society of Rice University Women, Buckyballs, Jan. 13, 1992; 249718 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - American Chemical Society, Doping the Fullerenes, Jan. 15-17, 1992; 249717 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Nanotechnology Conference, Japan, Getting Inside the Cage, Jan. 27-28, 1992; 249716 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Italian Workshop on Fullerenes, Doping the Fullerenes, Feb. 6-7, 1992; 249715 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Carnegie Mellon University Physics Department, Dopeyballs, Feb. 10, 1992; 249714 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Ohio State University Chemistry Department, Dopyballs, Feb. 11, 1992; 249713 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Louisiana State University Department of Physics and Astronomy, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, Feb. 26-29, 1992; 249712 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - MIT, Tinker Toy Surface Science, Semiconductor Nanocrystals, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, March 2-6, 1992; 249711 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Case Western University, Doping the Fullerenes, March 12, 1992; 249710 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - American Physical Society, International Prize for New Materials, March 16-22, 1992; 249709 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - University of Kansas Chemistry Department, University of Iowa Chemistry Department, March 17, 1992; Spring 1992; 249708 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Texas Tech University Physics Department, Doping the Fullerenes, March 26, 1992; 249707 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - University of South Dakota Chemistry Department, Buckyballs, March 30, 1992; 249706 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - American Chemical Society, March 31, 1992; 249705 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University Chemistry Department, Grappling with the Beast, Doping the Fullerenes, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, April 13, 1992; 249704 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - University of Texas Departments of Chemistry and Physics, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, April 22, 1992; 249703 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Rice University Hill Country Rice Alumni, Buckyballs: Great Balls of Carbon, April 22, 1992; 249702 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - University of North Carolina, Grappling with the Beast, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, April 1992; 249701 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - University of Wisconsin, University of California Berkeley, Doping the Fullerenes, May 8, 1992; May 6, 1992; 249700 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Wesleyan University Leermakers Symposium, M @ C 60, May 12, 1992; 249699 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Belgian Physical Society, Doping the Fullerenes, May 20, 1992; 249698 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Chalmers University and Stockholm, May 25-28, 1992; 249697 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - American Society for Mass Spectrometry, FT-ICR and the Metallo-Fullerenes, May 31-June 5, 1992; 249696 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - International Symposium on Molecular Beams, Doping the Fullerenes, June 10, 1992; 249695 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - National Technological University, Self-Assembly of the Fullerenes, June 23, 1992; 249694 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Clusters and Fullerenes Conference, June 23-26, 1992; 249693 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Tel Aviv University, Grappling with the Beast, Doping the Fullerenes, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, June 28-July 3, 1992; 249692 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - International School of Physics, Nanotechnology and the Fullerenes, Discovery of the Fullerenes, Electronic Quantum Size Effects, July 7-17, 1992; 249691 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - International Centre for Theoretical Physics," C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, July 10-11, 1992; 249690 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - International Symposium on Novel Aromatic Compounds, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, July 19-24, 1992; 249689 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Southwest Research Institute, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, Aug. 5, 1992; 249688 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Atomic and Nanoscale Modification conference, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, Aug. 16-21, 1992; 249687 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - American Chemical Society, Surface Chemistry on Transition Metal Clusters-Evidence for Shell Effect, Aug. 1992; 249686 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Hoechst Celanese, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, Sept. 2, 1992; 249685 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Department of Energy E.O. Lawrence Award, Sept. 16, 1992; 249684 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - World Techno Fair in China, Fullerene Nanotechnology, Sept. 18-19, 1992; 249683 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Materials Research Society Symposium, Spring 1992; 249682 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - American Chemical Society, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, Oct. 1, 1992; 249681 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - NEC Symposium, From Dopyballs to Nanowires, Oct. 11-15, 1992; 249680 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Rice Chemistry Faculty Retreat, Oct. 17-18, 1992; 249679 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - University of Pennsylvania, Oct. 20-21, 1992; 249678 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - American Chemical Society, Southwest Regional Award, Oct. 22, 1992; 1992; 249677 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Welch Award, Oct. 26-27, 1992; 249676 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - American Physical Society, Nov. 7, 1992; 249675 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - University of Wyoming, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, Nov. 13, 1992; 249674 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - University of South Florida, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, Nov. 19, 1992; 249673 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Princeton University, Dec. 2-4, 1992; 249672 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - American Association of Physics Teachers, Jan. 5, 1993; 249671 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Coast Guard Academy, Nanotechnology, Feb. 10, 1993; 249670 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, Feb. 12, 1993; 249669 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - University of California at Berkeley, Carbon Clusters, Nanotechnology and the Future of Chemistry, Feb. 16, 1993; 249668 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Society for Applied Spectroscopy, Spectral Probes of Fullerenes and other Nanoclusters, Feb. 23, 1993; 249667 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - UOP Research Center, Feb. 24, 1993; 249666 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - American Chemical Society, William H. Nichols Medal, March 12, 1993; 249665 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Lake Forest College, Clusters, Chemistry and Nanotechnology, March 22, 1993; 249664 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - American Physical Society, March 23-24, 1993; 249663 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Committee on Science, Space and Technology, Buckyballs and Nanotechnology, April 1, 1993; 249662 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - U.S. Naval Academy, Buckyballs, April 2, 1993; 249661 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - University of Nebraska, Carbon Clusters and the Challenge of Nanotechnology, April 30, 1993; 249660 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Auburn University, Carbon, Nanotechnology, and the Future of Chemistry, May 5, 1993; 249659 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - American Physical Society, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, May 17-19, 1993; 249658 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Science and Technology of the Fullerenes, June 27-July 1, 1993; 249657 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Physics and Chemistry of C 60 Seminar, Solar Generation of the Fullerenes, July 19-23, 1993; 249656 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - National Institute of Standards and Technology, Carbon's Role in Nanotechnology, Sept. 10, 1993; 249655 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Princeton University, Grapping with the Beast of Surface Science, Doping the Fullerenes, Carbon, Fibers, and Nanotechnology, Sept. 20-23, 1993; 249654 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Mexican Materials Society, Buckyballs and Nanotechnology, Oct. 1, 1993; 249653 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Oct. 6, 1993; 249652 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Ethyl Corporation, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, Oct. 8, 1993; 249651 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Electrochemical Society, From Buckyballs to Buckytubes: New Possibilities in Nanotechnology, Oct. 11, 1993; 249650 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Washington State University, Buckyballs and Nanotechnology, Oct. 26, 1993; 249649 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - [Rice] President's Inaugural Ceremony, Oct. 29-30, 1993; 249648 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Argonne National Laboratory, Buckyballs and Nanotechnology, Nov. 12, 1993; 249647 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Houston Museum of Natural Science, From Buckyball to Space Elevators, Nov. 12, 1993; 249646 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - University of Wyoming Dept. of Chemistry, C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology, Nov. 13, 1993; 249645 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - John Scott Award, Nov. 19, 1993; 249644 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Pennsylvania State University, Nov. 21-23, 1993; 249643 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Pennsylvania State University, Carbon's Role in Nanotechnology, Both Wet and Dry, Nov. 22, 1993; 249642 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Materials Research Society, On the Crystallization of Carbon in O, 1, and 2 Dimensions, Nov. 29-Dec. 2, 1993; 249641 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Series II: Correspondence, 1992-1996; 249626
  Includes general correspondence, incoming and outgoing mail, awards nominations, grants, patents and publishers correspondence all dealing with fullerenes or "buckyballs."
  - General, 1992; 249639 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - General, 1993; 249638 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, 1993; 249637 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, 1994; 249636 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, 1994; 249635 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, 1995; 249634 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, 1995; 249633 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, 1996; 249632 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, 1996; 249631 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Awards nominations, 249630 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Grants, 249629 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Patents, 249628 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Publishers, 249627 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Series III: Articles and Reprints, 1990-1998; 249619
  Articles and reprints related to buckyballs and nanotechnology, with a bibliography on the discovery.
  - Buckyball articles, 249625 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Metal cluster research articles, 249624 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Nanotechnology-related articles, 249623 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Reprints, 249622 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Authorization for reprint of articles, 249621 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Buckminsterfullerene bibliography, 249620 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Series IV: Personal, 1990-1998; 249612
  This series includes materials on awards, presentations and daily calendars.
  - Awards-articles and programs, 249618 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Presentations listings, 249617 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Baker & Botts promotional booklet with Smalley photo, 249616 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Monthly/yearly appointment book, 1990-1994; 249615 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Monthly/yearly appointment book, 1991-1994; 249614 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Monthly/yearly appointment book, 1995-1998; 249613 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Series V: Chemistry 102 Lecture Notes, Problem Sets, and Exams, 1994-1997, n.d.; 249596
  Scope and Contents Note
  This series contains lecture notes, problem sets,and exams for the Chemistry 102 classes Dr. Smalley taught at Rice University from 1995-1997.
  - Chem 102 Problem Sets and Exams, 1994-1996; 249611 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Chem 102 Solutions to Problem Sets and Exams, 1996, n.d.; 249610 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Chem 102 Math Review Toolkit and Lectures 35-38, 1994-1996; 249609 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Chem 102 1995 Lecture Notes 1/4, 249608 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Chem 102 1995 Lecture Notes 2/4, 249607 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Chem 102 1995 Lecture Notes 3/4, 249606 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Chem 102 1995 Lecture Notes 4/4, 249605 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Chem 102 1996 Lecture Notes 1/5, 249604 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Chem 102 1996 Lecture Notes 2/5, 249603 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Chem 102 1996 Lecture Notes 3/5, 249602 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Chem 102 1996 Lecture Notes 4/5, 249601 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Chem 102 1996 Lecture Notes 5/5, 249600 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Chem 102 1997 Lecture Notes 1/3, 249599 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Chem 102 1997 Lecture Notes 2/3, 249598 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Chem 102 1997 Lecture Notes 3/3, 249597 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Series VI: Finding Aid and Container List for Richard E. Smalley Papers, Chemical Heritage Foundation Archives, 2006; 249594
  Finding Aid and Container List for the Richard E. Smalley Papers held at the Chemical Heritage Foundation Archives.
  - Finding Aid and Container List for Richard E. Smalley Papers, Chemical Heritage Foundation Archives, 2006; 249595 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Series VII: Lectures, Presentations, and Conferences, 1994 - 2002; 249504
  Separated Materials
  Nobel Prize Certificate (Box 7 Folder 82) removed and placed in WRC vault.
  - Asia trip (cancelled), Spring 1994; 249593 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Florida State University Dept of Chemistry Spring Seminar (cancelled), Spring 1994; 249592 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Naval Research Laboratory External Core Review Panel (Chemical Dynamics and Diagnostics), January 9-11, 1994; 249591 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Puerto Rico Interdisciplinary Science Meeting, "Buckyballs and Nanotechnology", March 4-5, 1994; 249590 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Shenandoah University, Warrington Science Lecture Series, "Carbon's Role in Nanotechnology (Both Wet and Dry)", March 25-26, 1994; 249589 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - European Physical Society, Hewlett Packard Europhysics Prize, March 30, 1994; 249588 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Texas A & M University Kingsville, Fred M. Garland Memorial Lecture, "Buckyballs and the New Carbon-based Nanotechnology", April 14, 1994; 249587 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - University of California Santa Barbara, Chemistry Dept Building Dedication, "Buckyballs and the New Carbon-based Nanotechnology", May 20, 1994; 249586 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - C-SPAN: Science Kicks '94, Tribute to Dr. Buckminster Fuller, May 23, 1994; 249585 (Box 7, Folder 9)